Science created him. Now Chuck Norris must destroy him.
Silent Rage is a action, horror, science fiction
film directed by Michael Miller.
A mentally ill man in a small Texas town goes on a killing
rampage and is fatally wounded by police.
When doctors use an experimental serum to bring him back to life, the killer
develops superhuman strength and the town sheriff must pursue him.
Sheriff Dan Stevens, played by Chuck Norris.
Dr. Tom Halman, played by Ron Silver.
Alison Halman, played by Toni Kalem.
John Kirby, played by Brian Libby.
Dr. Philip Spires, played by Steven Keats.
Dr. Paul Vaughn, played by William Finley.
Silent Rage is a 1982 American sci-fi action horror
film directed by Michael Miller.
It stars Chuck Norris as a sheriff who must stop a mentally ill man (Brian Libby) who goes
on a rampage after being granted indestructibility in a medical experiment.
It grossed $10.5 million on release.
The film explores themes of small town, martial
arts, kung fu, showdown, sheriff.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and emotional.